mobotalks.com 2015-02-27

# Privacy Policy | MoboTalks

**[Privacy Policy](http://mobotalks.com/privacy-policy/) for www.mobotalks.com**

MoboTalks.com values our readers privacy .How ever we do collect our readers information to improve our website and to collect statistics of visitors info for our website we use Google Analytics .We never share our readers information with third parties .Your privacy is very important to us.

If you have any doubt concerned with our website [privacy policy](http://mobotalks.com/privacy-policy/) or software, please feel free to [contact us](http://mobotalks.com/contact-us/). Please read our Privacy Policy below to learn more about how we treat personally identifiable information, how it is protected and used.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.mobotalks.com does not use cookies. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense and Infolinks.

**Copyright Policy**

We don’t have any. You are free to use and copy any content from our site BUT, you must provide credit links on the pages you’ve copied or used our content.Note : Since we accept user submissions, If any of our Articles or content infringe your copyright, then [contact us](http://mobotalks.com/contact-us/) immediately at the email provided.

**Third Party Advertising:**

We use third party advertising companies to display advertisement on this site. They may use cookies to serve ads on this site and use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Internet Based advertising**

Since Google sooner going to display ads based on interests of user,that is if you visit sports related websites regularly which have Google adsense ads ,you will be grouped as “sport enthusiast” category .This is Internet Advertising approach from Google for this they collect some info which do not include your name ,email-id,phone number, address or any such details .You may read about that [here.](http://adsense.blogspot.com/2009/03/driving-monetization-with-ads-that.html)

**External Links:**

This web site contains many links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

>> **Contact US : mobotalks@gmail.com**
